Danny Kaye and Sylvia Fine Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Music, 1939-1985 (Box 1-427, 536-537, 641-765, 791)
  - The Danny Kaye Show, 1963-1967 (Box 1-282, 695-766)
    - Episode #101, 1966, October 5, 95518307
      - All you pretty people (Box-folder 233/1, 743/7)
      - Danny-Ella medley (Box-folder 233/2-4, 234/1-2, 743/8)
      - December and May (Box-folder 234/3, 743/9)
      - Irish Kaye medley (Box-folder 743/10)
      - Irish washerwoman (Box-folder 234/4, 744/1)
      - It don't mean a thing (Box-folder 234/5, 744/2)
      - Mood indigo (Box-folder 235/1, 744/3)
      - My wild Irish Kaye (Box-folder 235/2, 744/4)
      - Strip city blues (Box-folder 235/3, 744/5)
      - We like each other (Box-folder 235/4, 744/6)
      - We like each other (reprise) (Box-folder 235/5, 744/7)
    - Episode #102, 1966, October 19, 95518444
      - Glow worm (Box-folder 235/6, 744/8)
      - Hurry - its lovely up here (Box-folder 236/1, 744/9)
      - Italian playoff (Box-folder 236/2, 744/10)
      - A man's man (Box-folder 236/3, 744/11)
      - Thou swell (Box-folder 236/4-5, 744/12)
      - You've gotta move (Box-folder 237/1-2, 744/13)
    - Episode #103, 1966, December 28, 95518495
      - The battle of the bulge (Box-folder 237/3, 745/1)
      - Chime in (Box-folder 237/4-5, 238/1, 745/2)
      - Conversation in Bossa Nova (Box-folder 238/2, 745/3)
      - The frog and the grog (Box-folder 239/1, 745/4)
      - Instant spy (Box-folder 239/2, 745/5)
      - Stompin' at the Savoy (Box-folder 239/3-4, 240/1-2, 745/6)
    - Episode #104, 1966, November 16, 95518503
      - I'll remember April (Box-folder 240/3, 746/1)
      - It's today (Box-folder 241/1-2, 746/2)
      - Louis medley (Box-folder 241/3-4)
      - Salute to Louis (Box-folder 242/1-2, 746/3)
      - The shadow of your smile (Box-folder 242/3, 746/4)
      - White heat episode (Box-folder 242/4, 746/5)
    - Episode #105, 1966, November 2, 95518574
      - Answering service (Box-folder 243/1, 747/1)
      - High school reunion (Box-folder 243/2, 747/2)
      - I must know (Box-folder 243/3, 747/3)
      - Sunny disposish medley (Box-folder 243/4-5, 747/4)
      - Tiger rag (Box-folder 244/1, 747/5)
      - Vickie (Box-folder 244/2, 747/6)
    - Episode #106, 1967, January 11, 95518650
      - Giovanni's room (Box-folder 244/3, 747/7)
      - It takes two (Box-folder 244/4, 747/8)
      - Senior citizen (Box-folder 245/1, 747/9)
      - Style (Box-folder 245/2-3, 747/10)
    - Episode #107, 1967, January 4, 95518809
      - Aren't you glad you're you (Box-folder 246/1, 748/1)
      - The five pennies saints (Box-folder 748/2)
      - Io e te (Box-folder 246/2, 748/3)
      - Ipanema (Box-folder 246/3, 748/4)
      - Jerome's Birthday (Box-folder 247/1, 748/5)
      - The Jules Jacques March (Box-folder 247/2)
      - Scottish doctor (Box-folder 247/3, 748/6)
    - Episode #108, 1966, November 23, 95518916
      - The music halls (Box-folder 247/4, 248/1-2, 748/7)
      - Sailing away (Box-folder 248/3-4, 749/1)
      - Time interlude (Box-folder 248/5, 749/2)
      - Today I love everybody (Box-folder 249/1, 749/3)
      - Two rivers (Box-folder 249/2, 749/4)
      - Who killed Cock Robin (Box-folder 249/3-4, 749/5)
      - You do something to me (Box-folder 250/1, 749/6)
    - Episode #109, 1966, November 30, 95518972
      - All of me (Box-folder 250/2, 749/7)
      - Capsule movies (Box-folder 250/3, 749/8)
      - Czardas (Box-folder 251/1-2, 749/9)
      - It all started with the wheel (Box-folder 251/3-4, 750/1)
      - The magnificent two (Box-folder 252/1, 750/2)
      - The old tycoon (Box-folder 252/2, 750/3)
      - Turkey in the straw (Box-folder 252/3)
    - Episode #110, 1966, December 7, 95518983
      - Jerome's help (Box-folder 252/4, 750/4)
      - Lost letter - walk on the wild side (Box-folder 252/5-6, 750/5)
      - Nothing can stop me now (Box-folder 253/1, 750/6)
      - Walking happy (Box-folder 253/2, 750/7)
      - What's new at the zoo (Box-folder 253/3, 750/8)
    - Episode #111, 1966, December 14, 95519058
      - Ammore mio (Box-folder 254/1, 751/1)
      - Arab dance (Box-folder 254/2, 751/2)
      - English home (Box-folder 254/3, 751/3)
      - For me and my gal (Box-folder 254/4, 751/4)
      - He loves me (Box-folder 254/5-6, 751/5)
      - I'll never smile (Box-folder 255/1, 751/6)
      - The joker (Box-folder 255/2)
      - The mouse patrol (Box-folder 255/3, 751/7)
      - Operatic routine (Box-folder 255/4, 751/8)
      - Prop dance (Box-folder 256/1-2, 751/9)
      - Smile again (Box-folder 751/10)
      - The sound of words (Box-folder 256/3, 751/11)
    - Episode #112, 1966, December 21, 95519065
      - The bicycle (Box-folder 257/1, 752/1)
      - Christmas tree (Box-folder 257/2, 752/2)
      - I love the outdoors (Box-folder 257/3, 752/3)
      - Some children (Box-folder 257/4, 752/4)
      - Waltz around the Christmas tree (Box-folder 257/5-6, 752/5)
    - Episode #113, 1967, March 1, 95519401
      - Ain't misbehavin' (Box-folder 258/1, 752/6)
      - All of a sudden (Box-folder 258/2, 752/7)
      - Brother John (Box-folder 258/3-4)
      - Cabaret (Box-folder 259/1-2, 752/8)
      - Dance brother dance, Other title: Dance brother dance John (Box-folder 752/9)
      - I'll buy the ring (Box-folder 753/1)
      - Lily of the valley (Box-folder 753/2)
      - Number on my house (Box-folder 753/3)
      - Swanee river (Box-folder 259/3, 753/4)
      - Yankee Doodle blues (Box-folder 259/4, 753/5)
    - Episode #114, 1967, January 18, 95519490
      - Come dance with me (Box-folder 260/1-2, 753/6)
      - Down by the station (Box-folder 260/3-5, 753/7)
      - Vignettes (Box-folder 261/1, 753/8)
    - Episode #115, 1967, January 25, 95519496
      - I'm a brass band (Box-folder 261/2-3, 753/9)
      - Lonesome road (Box-folder 262/1-2, 754/1)
      - Soap opera blues (Box-folder 262/3, 754/2)
      - Teamwork (Box-folder 262/4-5, 754/3)
    - Episode #116, 1967, February 15, 95519560
      - The continental (Box-folder 263/1-2, 754/4)
      - The easy way (Box-folder 263/3)
      - Lonely again (Box-folder 263/4)
      - The rules of the road (Box-folder 264/1, 754/5)
      - There's always an extra potato (Box-folder 264/2-3, 754/6)
      - Western medley (Box-folder 265/1-2, 754/7)
      - Who can I turn to (Box-folder 265/3, 754/8)
    - Episode #117, 1967, February 1, 95519568
      - All the world is a stage, Includes "I just found girls (Teenage lover)" (Box-folder 266/1-3, 755/1)
      - Any Wednesday (Box-folder 267/1-2, 755/2)
      - Lonesome (Box-folder 267/3, 755/3)
      - Man with a golden arm (Box-folder 268/1, 755/4)
      - Mr. make-up man (Box-folder 268/2, 755/5)
      - Plant a radish (Box-folder 268/3, 755/6)
      - Where are our children (Box-folder 268/4, 755/7)
    - Episode #118, 1967, February 22, 95519821
      - Ami ami (Box-folder 269/1, 756/1)
      - Chi chi pa (Box-folder 756/2)
      - The monkey band (Box-folder 269/2, 756/3)
      - Parade (intro) (Box-folder 269/3, 756/4)
      - Where do you work-a John (Box-folder 269/4-6, 756/5)
      - Work dance "heigh ho" (Box-folder 270/1-3, 756/6)
    - Episode #119, 1967, March 8, 95519945
      - I'm a no jealous (Box-folder 270/4, 756/7)
      - Italian medley (Box-folder 271/1-2, 756/8)
      - Italian wedding song (E flat) (Box-folder 271/3, 757/1)
      - Italian wedding song (F) (Box-folder 271/4, 272/1)
      - Let me entertain you (Box-folder 272/2-3, 757/2)
      - Married (Box-folder 272/4, 757/3)
      - Too old to be young (Box-folder 273/1, 757/4)
      - Too old to be young (reprise) (Box-folder 273/2, 757/5)
      - Waltz (intro) (Box-folder 273/3, 757/6)
      - What does she mean by that (Box-folder 273/4, 757/7)
    - Episode #120, 1967, April 5, 95520054
      - Dr. Zhivago (Box-folder 274/1-3, 757/8)
      - Interlude (Box-folder 274/4, 757/9)
      - Let's not talk about love (Box-folder 275/1, 758/1)
      - L-o-v-e (Box-folder 275/2-3, 758/2)
      - Tarantella (Box-folder 275/4, 758/3)
      - Where am I going (Box-folder 275/5, 758/4)
      - Winchester Cathedral (Box-folder 275/6, 758/5)
    - Episode #121, 1967, March 15, 95520063
      - Big beautiful ball (Box-folder 276/1-2)
      - Flash, bang, wallop (Box-folder 276/3, 758/6)
      - Roman spectacle (Box-folder 276/4, 758/7)
    - Episode #122, 1967, March 29, 95520157
      - 2nd act opening (Box-folder 277/1, 758/8)
      - Be yourself (Box-folder 277/2, 758/9)
      - Boat film (Box-folder 277/3, 758/10)
      - Caribbean cruise (Box-folder 277/4, 758/11)
      - Caribbean opening (Box-folder 278/1-2, 759/1)
      - Don't look now! (Box-folder 278/3, 759/2)
      - Finale - Jerome (Box-folder 278/4, 759/3)
      - I like you (Box-folder 279/1, 759/4)
      - I like you (reprise) (Box-folder 279/2, 759/5)
      - Jamaica farewell (Box-folder 759/6)
      - Shy-type person (Box-folder 279/3, 759/7)
      - Waltz playoff (Box-folder 279/4, 759/8)
    - Episode #123, 1967, March 22, 95520282
      - Barefoot contessa (Box-folder 279/5)
      - Color my world (Box-folder 280/1-2, 759/9)
      - Huff and a puff (Box-folder 280/3, 759/10)
      - Oinka-oinka (Box-folder 280/4, 759/11)
      - Pig playoff (Box-folder 280/5, 759/12)
      - Three link sausages (Box-folder 280/6, 759/13)
    - Episode #124, 1967, April 12, 95520319
      - This old man (Box-folder 281/1, 760/1)
      - Walking on new grass, Other title: Walking on the grass (Box-folder 281/2-3, 760/2)
      - A wonderful day like today (Box-folder 281/4, 282/1-2, 760/3)
      - A wonderful day medley, Choir part only. (Box-folder 282/4)
  - The Danny Kaye Tour Library, 1940s-1980s (Box 283-538, 760-763)
    Parts (boxes 283-358) and score arrangements (boxes 760-763) for music used by Kaye in his stage performances. Some titles are composed by Fine. If only parts or score arrangements are available, just the respective boxes are listed.
    Arranged alphabetically by song title.
    - Ach du lieber (Box-folder 283/1)
    - Airy fairy pipers (Box-folder 283/2)
    - Airy fairy tales (Box-folder 283/3)
    - All the world is a stage (Box-folder 283/4-6)
    - Ami ami (Box-folder 284/1)
    - Anatole of Paris (Box-folder 284/2)
    - Ballin' the Jack (Box-folder 284/3-4)
    - Ballin the jack (closing) (Box-folder 284/5)
    - Barber shop (Box-folder 284/6)
    - Baseball man, Arranged by Bob Alberti. (Box-folder 284/7, 760/4)
    - Bathtub admiral (Box-folder 284/8)
    - Battle hymn (Box-folder 284/9)
    - Begin the beguine (Box-folder 285/1)
    - Candy kisses (Box-folder 285/2)
    - Carnival of Venice (Box-folder 285/3-4)
    - Carnival of Venice jazz (Box-folder 285/5)
    - Casey (Box-folder 627, 760/5)
    - Chi chi pa (Box-folder 285/6)
    - Ciu ciu bella (Box-folder 760/6)
    - Cotton fields - blue tail fly (Box-folder 285/7)
    - Crazy Barbara (Box-folder 285/8)
    - Danny Kaye entrance (Box-folder 286/1)
    - Danny Kaye overture (Box-folder 286/2)
    - Deck the halls (Box-folder 286/3)
    - Deenah (Box-folder 286/4)
    - Dem bones (Box-folder 286/5-6)
    - Dinah walk on (Box-folder 286/7)
    - Do you ever think of me (Box-folder 287/1-2)
    - Drink, gypsy, Includes orchestral parts for theatrical version. (Box-folder 287/3-5, 762/4)
    - Dunhill bit, 4th trumpet part only. (Box-folder 287/6)
    - The first noel (Box-folder 288/1)
    - Flamenco (Box-folder 288/2)
    - Flea (Box-folder 288/3)
    - Folk song medley (Box-folder 288/4)
    - French intro (Box-folder 288/5)
    - German concert song (Box-folder 288/6)
    - Glory hallelujah twist (Box-folder 288/7)
    - Good King Wenceslas (Box-folder 288/8)
    - Great come and get it day (Box-folder 289/1)
    - Ha shalom (Box-folder 289/2)
    - Hawaiian-African, Empty folder.; On folder: All tacit. (Box-folder 289/3)
    - I belong to Glasgow (Box-folder 289/4)
    - I can't stop loving you (Box-folder 761/1)
    - I like old people (Box-folder 289/5)
    - I'd love to call you rose (Box-folder 289/6)
    - I'll buy the ring (Box-folder 289/7)
    - I'm five & Coda (Box-folder 289/8)
    - I've got a loverly bunch (Box-folder 290/1-2, 761/2)
    - The inch worm sequence (Box-folder 290/3)
    - Jamaica farewell (Box-folder 290/4)
    - January (Box-folder 290/5)
    - Japanese song (Box-folder 290/6)
    - Just in time (Box-folder 291/1-2)
    - Kent commercial (Box-folder 291/3)
    - Korea (Box-folder 291/4)
    - Let there be peace (Box-folder 291/5)
    - Life could not better be (Box-folder 291/6)
    - Lily of the valley (Box-folder 292/1)
    - The little white duck (Box-folder 292/2)
    - Lonely again (Box-folder 292/3)
    - Lonesome road (Box-folder 292/4)
    - Look sharp - be sharp, Boston Pops orchestra arrangement. (Box-folder 292/5)
    - Madam - Crepe Suzette (Box-folder 292/6)
    - Man in my life (Box-folder 293/1)
    - Medley (Box-folder 293/2)
    - Melody in 4F (Box-folder 293/3)
    - Minnie the Moocher (Box-folder 293/4-6, 761/3)
    - Mona Luigi's (Box-folder 761/4)
    - New baby (Box-folder 294/1)
    - Neutral playoffs (Box-folder 294/2)
    - Night and day (Box-folder 294/3)
    - Nonsense songs (Box-folder 294/4-5, 295/1)
    - The number on my house, Other title: I forgot the number on my house (Box-folder 295/2)
    - Oh cha chornia (Dark eyes) (Box-folder 295/3)
    - Oh come all ye faithful (Box-folder 295/4)
    - P.S. 149 (Box-folder 295/5)
    - Pavlova (Box-folder 295/6)
    - Peony bush (Box-folder 295/7)
    - The puddle (Box-folder 295/8)
    - Saints (Box-folder 295/9)
    - Seven ages overture (Box-folder 296/1)
    - Shickfitz, Lyrics by Sylvia Fine and Herb Baker, music by Sylvia Fine; Other title: Stickfitz (Box-folder 296/2-3)
    - Sho sho (Box-folder 296/4)
    - Sometimes I'm happy (Box-folder 297/1)
    - South Rampart Street parade (Box-folder 297/2)
    - Spanish flea (Box-folder 297/3)
    - Stanislovsky (Box-folder 297/4)
    - Story (Box-folder 298/1)
    - Spiritual (Box-folder 761/5)
    - Sunshine, lollipops and rainbows (Box-folder 298/2)
    - Tall hope (Box-folder 298/3-4)
    - Thank you letter (Box-folder 298/5)
    - Thirties production, Contents: Everything I have is yours; Beguine; Ever see a dream walking; Broadway; 42nd street. (Box-folder 299/1-3)
    - Thumbelina (Box-folder 299/4)
    - Time after time (Box-folder 762/5)
    - The triplets (Box-folder 299/5)
    - True or false - false or true (Box-folder 299/6)
    - Tschaikowsky (Box-folder 299/7)
    - Turn around (Box-folder 300/1)
    - The ugly duckling (Box-folder 300/2)
    - Waltzing Matilda (Box-folder 300/3)
    - We wish you a merry Christmas (Box-folder 300/4)
    - Wee Doch 'n Dorris (We Deoch and Dorris) (Box-folder 300/5-6, 761/6)
    - Wee Hughie (Box-folder 300/7)
    - Will ye no come back again? (Box-folder 300/8)
    - Wonderful Copenhagen (Box-folder 300/9)
    - Yogi (Box-folder 300/10)
    - Yogi (intro) (Box-folder 300/11)
    - Young and foolish (Box-folder 761/7)
  - An Evening with Danny Kaye, 1950s-1980s
    Conducting scores (box 301) and orchestral parts (boxes 302-309) for music used by Danny Kaye in his conducting performances.
    Conducting scores are arranged alphabetically by composer last name; orchestral parts are arranged in folders by instrument.
    Contents:
    Alford, Kenneth J. Colonel Bogey march
    Alven, Hugo. Midsommarvaka, op.19
    Anderson, Leroy. Fiddle faddle
    Beethoven, Ludwig van. Symphony no. 5 in C minor, op.67
    Beethoven, Ludwig van. Achte Symphonie
    Emerson, Walter. Carnival of Venice
    Fine, Sylvia. Airy fairy pipers
    Fine, Sylvia. Begin the beguine
    Fine, Sylvia. Flamenco
    Fine, Sylvia. The German concert song
    Fine, Sylvia. Pavlova
    Hurst, Michael. Waltzing Matilda
    Merrick, Mahlon. Look sharp march
    Murphy, C.W., Dan Lipton and John Neat. She's a lassie from Lancashire
    Ponchielli, Amilcare. Dance of the hours
    Ravel, Maurice. Bolero
    Rimsky-Korsakov, Nickolay. The flight of the bumblebee
    Rossini, Gioacchino. Ouverture zur oper "Die diebische Elster"
    Schubert, Franz. Siebente symphonie in C major
    Schreiber. The Danny Kaye polka
    Sousa, John Philip. The stars and stripes forever
    Strauss, Johann. Tritsch-trasch (Chit-chat) polka
    Strauss, Johann. Die fledermaus (du und du)
    Tschaikowsky, Peter Ilich. The nutcracker-suite, op.71a
    Verdi, Giuseppe. Triumphal march from Aida
    Wagner, Richard. Einleitung zum dritten akt der oper Lohengrin
  - The John Gary Show, 1966
    Parts (boxes 310-357) and scores (boxes 641-672) for music performed in the John Gary Show. If only parts or full score arrangements exist, just the respective boxes are listed.
    - Alfie (Box-folder 641/1)
    - All the things you are (Box-folder 310/1, 641/2)
    - Alouette (Box-folder 310/2)
    - And that reminds me (Box-folder 310/3)
    - Anytime (Box-folder 310/4, 641/3)
    - As long as I'm singin' (Box-folder 310/5, 641/4)
    - Be back soon (Box-folder 310/6)
    - Be my love (Box-folder 310/7, 641/5)
    - Beautiful (Box-folder 311/1, 641/6)
    - Beautiful baby playoff (Box-folder 311/2, 641/7)
    - Because of you (Box-folder 311/3, 641/8)
    - Bella bella (Box-folder 311/4, 642/1)
    - The best is yet to come (Box-folder 311/5, 642/2)
    - Best thing for you (Box-folder 312/1-2, 642/3)
    - Big spender (Box-folder 312/3, 642/4)
    - Blues in the night (Box-folder 312/4, 642/5)
    - Call me (Box-folder 312/5, 643/1)
    - Charlie my boy (Box-folder 312/6)
    - Cheerio finale, Includes "A nightingale sang in the Berk'ley square" and "Knees up-Mamma Brown." (Box-folder 313/1)
    - Children go (Box-folder 313/2)
    - Clancy (1, 2, 3) (Box-folder 313/3)
    - Cockles & mussels (Box-folder 313/4, 643/2)
    - Come to me - bend to me (Box-folder 313/5, 643/3)
    - Cotton fields (Box-folder 313/6-7, 643/4)
    - Crosby playoff (Box-folder 313/8, 643/5)
    - Cute (Box-folder 314/1, 643/6)
    - Danny boy (Box-folder 314/2, 643/7)
    - Dear hearts #1 (Box-folder 314/3, 644/1)
    - Dear hearts #3 (Box-folder 314/4, 644/2)
    - Dear hearts #5 (Box-folder 314/5, 644/3)
    - Distant shores (Box-folder 314/6, 644/4)
    - Dixie (Box-folder 314/7)
    - Doe, a deer (Box-folder 315/1, 644/5)
    - Don't let the rain come down (Box-folder 315/2, 644/6)
    - Don't rain on my parade (Box-folder 315/3, 644/7)
    - Don't you touch my hair (Box-folder 315/4, 644/8)
    - Elegance (Box-folder 316/1-2, 645/1)
    - England production (Box-folder 316/3-5, 317/1-2, 645/2-3, 646/1)
    - Espana rhapsody (Box-folder 317/3-4, 646/2)
    - Exodus (Box-folder 317/5)
    - Fair productions (Box-folder 318/1)
    - Fiddler on the roof (Box-folder 318/2-4, 647/1-3)
    - The flying saucer song (Box-folder 319/1, 648/1)
    - Georgia (Box-folder 319/2)
    - Go ahead & cry (Box-folder 319/3)
    - Goin' out of my head, Other title: Goin' out of my mind (Box-folder 319/4, 648/2)
    - Goin' to Chicago blues (Box-folder 319/5, 648/3)
    - Granada (Box-folder 319/6, 648/4)
    - Green peppers (Box-folder 319/7, 648/5)
    - Hair (Box-folder 320/1, 649/1)
    - He's got the whole world (Box-folder 320/2)
    - Hello young lovers (Box-folder 320/3, 649/2)
    - Hogan's heroes march (Box-folder 320/4, 649/3)
    - Hogan's heroes march (intro) (Box-folder 320/5, 649/4)
    - Hot diggety (Box-folder 320/6)
    - How little we know (Box-folder 320/7, 649/5)
    - I ain't down yet (Box-folder 321/1-2, 649/6)
    - I believe (Box-folder 321/3, 650/1)
    - I can't believe (Box-folder 321/4)
    - I hear music (Box-folder 321/5, 650/2)
    - I love Paris (Box-folder 321/6)
    - I'm all smiles (Box-folder 322/1, 650/3)
    - I'm always chasing rainbows (Box-folder 322/2)
    - I'm gonna live 'till I die (Box-folder 322/3, 650/4)
    - Iddy biddy baby (Box-folder 322/4)
    - If (Box-folder 322/5, 650/5)
    - If ever I would leave (Box-folder 650/6)
    - If you love me (Box-folder 322/6, 650/7)
    - Impressions (Box-folder 322/7-8, 651/1)
    - Intro - Chad & Jeremy (Box-folder 323/1, 651/2)
    - Irish eyes play-off (Box-folder 323/2, 651/3)
    - Irish production (section 1 & 2) (Box-folder 323/3-4, 324/1-4, 651/4-5)
    - It's over (Box-folder 325/1)
    - Italian play on (Box-folder 325/2, 652/1)
    - Italian production (section 1 & 2) (Box-folder 325/3-5, 326/1-3, 652/2-3)
    - J. Byner spot (Box-folder 327/1, 653/1)
    - Jamaica farewell (Box-folder 327/2, 653/2)
    - Jehosophat (Box-folder 327/3-4, 653/3)
    - Jules M. play on (Box-folder 327/5, 653/4)
    - Knees up Momma Brown (Box-folder 327/6)
    - Let there be peace (Box-folder 328/1)
    - A little bit of heaven (Box-folder 653/5)
    - The lonely goatherd (Box-folder 328/2, 653/6)
    - Look at that face (Box-folder 328/3)
    - Love is a many splendored thing (Box-folder 328/4, 653/7)
    - Love is just around the corner (Box-folder 328/5, 653/8)
    - Lovely way to spend an evening (Box-folder 328/6, 654/1)
    - Lover's concerto (Box-folder 328/7, 654/2)
    - Mama look a boo boo (Box-folder 329/1-2, 654/3)
    - Mame (Box-folder 329/3-4, 654/4)
    - Maria tonight (Box-folder 330/1-4, 654/5)
    - Matchmaker (Box-folder 330/5, 654/6)
    - Memoirs of a king (Box-folder 331/1, 655/1)
    - Mexican production (section 1 & 2) (Box-folder 331/2-6, 655/2-3)
    - Michelle (Box-folder 332/1, 655/4)
    - Minstrel production (Section 1 - 3) (Box-folder 332/2-5, 333/1-4, 656/1-3)
    - More (Box-folder 334/1-2, 656/4)
    - Movie theme (Box-folder 334/3, 656/5)
    - Nancy (Box-folder 334/4)
    - New beautiful baby (Box-folder 334/5)
    - New Rock-a-bye baby (Box-folder 334/6)
    - A nightingale sang in Berkley Square (Box-folder 334/7)
    - No arms can ever hold you (Box-folder 334/8, 656/6)
    - O sole mio (Box-folder 334/9)
    - Old MacDonald (Box-folder 334/10, 335/1-3, 657/1)
    - On a day like today (Box-folder 335/4, 657/2)
    - On a wonderful day (Box-folder 335/5)
    - On the street where you live (Box-folder 335/6, 657/3)
    - Once upon a summer time (Box-folder 336/1)
    - Once upon a time (Box-folder 336/2)
    - Paris spot (Box-folder 336/3-6, 337/1-4, 657/4, 658/1-2)
    - Penny a pitch (Box-folder 338/1)
    - A perfect day (Box-folder 338/2, 658/3)
    - Please don't talk to me (Box-folder 338/3)
    - Pops classics, Other title: Pops from classics ("I'm always chasing rainbows" and "Tonight we love") (Box-folder 338/4, 658/4-5)
    - Pops classics playoff (reprise) (Box-folder 338/5, 658/6)
    - Possum song (Box-folder 338/6)
    - Prisoner of love (Box-folder 338/7, 658/7)
    - Racing production (section 1 & 2) (Box-folder 339/1-4, 340/1-2, 659/1-2)
    - Red rosy bush (Box-folder 340/3, 659/3)
    - River medley (Box-folder 340/4-5, 341/1-2, 660/1-2)
    - Rock-a-bye baby play-off(on) (Box-folder 341/3, 660/3)
    - Shadow of your smile #2 (Box-folder 341/4, 661/1)
    - Shangri-la-lodge (Box-folder 341/5)
    - She loves me (Box-folder 341/6-7, 661/2)
    - Sitting on top of the world (Box-folder 342/1, 661/3)
    - Sloop John B. (Box-folder 342/2-3, 662/1)
    - Softly as I leave you (Box-folder 342/4)
    - Somethings gotta give (Box-folder 342/5, 343/1-2, 662/2)
    - Somewhere (Box-folder 343/3)
    - The song of the coo coo (Box-folder 343/4, 662/3)
    - The sound of music (Box-folder 343/5, 662/4)
    - Spiritual number (section 1 & 2) (Box-folder 343/6-7, 344/1-4, 663/1-2)
    - State Fair (section 1 & 2) (Box-folder 345/1-4, 346/1-2, 664/1-2)
    - Strangers in the night (Box-folder 346/3, 664/3)
    - Summer medley (Box-folder 347/1-4, 665/1)
    - Sunrise sunset (Box-folder 347/5, 665/2)
    - Take me in your arms (Box-folder 348/1, 666/1)
    - A taste of honey (Box-folder 348/2, 666/2)
    - Tea for two (ping pong) (Box-folder 348/3, 666/3)
    - Ten girls ago (Box-folder 348/4, 666/4)
    - Tender trap (Box-folder 348/5, 666/5)
    - That old gang of mine (Box-folder 348/6, 667/1)